Guide to the Yale University Master of Fine Arts Theses In Graphic Design
Yale University Arts Library
- Theses
  - Sunbathing & Graphic design., 1983; Coveney, Karen Salsgiver (Box 8)
  - Reflections on paintings as models for typgographic arrangements., 1983; Gluck, Chris (Box 8)
  - A visual grammar of writing., 1983; Dubberly, Hugh (Box 9)
  - Bookbinding without a bindery., 1983; Hoerner, Nancy (Box 9)
  - Color observed., 1983; Kohn, Judy (Box 29)
  - The contexual manipulation of visual symbols., 1983; Levine, Peter (Box 9)
  - Changing faces, facing changes: desiging the visual properties of a human-computer interface., 1983; Mehl, Richard (Box 24)
  - Computer graphic animation., 1983; Melilli, Mary (Box 9)
  - The transition pen to press: "Historia Fiorentina.", 1983; Myers, Chris (Box 9)
  - Serifa, 1983; Vassey, Andrew (Box 24)
  - Vehicle graphics: a study in form and function., 1984; Aronson, David; 2 (Box 9)
  - Anti War imagery., 1984; Aquadro, Jeana (Box 29)
  - Sara's day: (Videocassette), 1984; Bednar, Joseph; video (Box 9)
  - Metaphor: design., 1984; Dutlinger, Anne D. (Box 9)
  - Towards a working language of color., 1984; Ferrier, Christopher (Box 9)
  - Scientific diagrams: selected topics for designers., 1984; Grant, Angelynn J. (Box 9)
  - "After modern architecture" concerning buildings and graphic design., 1984; Guglietti, Joseph (Box 9)
  - The invisible woman: graphic aspects of gynecological instruction., 1984; Mayer, Nancy (Box 24)
  - Parallel chronologies of Japanese and occidental written forms, moji, 30,000 B.C. to 1,000 A.D., 1984; Niijima, Minoru (Box 30)
  - Trends in trademark design: a look at marks of identification in Western Europe and America., 1984; Obert, John (Box 9)
  - Bath., 1984; Ouchi, Lisa (Box 30)
    See also entry under 1986.
  - Vernacular typography of hand painted signs., 1984; Overmeyer, Don P. (Box 9)
  - Graphic problems and options in timetable design., 1984; Roseman, Barry (Box 9)
  - Lettra à Stephane Mallarmé., 1984; Seweryn, Elzbieta (Box 33)
  - Vizualizing music: considerations for graphic designers., 1984; Vaitkunas, George (Box 9)
  - The art exhibition poster., 1985; Alcala, Antonio (Box 9)
  - Mask: a design process., 1985; Anton, William J. (Box 30)
  - Modes of expression in graphic design., 1985; Bacchus, Derek (Box 9)
  - Architecture and graphic design., 1985; Cameron, Tracey (Box 9)
  - Alphabet soup: English orthography and its effects on literacy., 1985; Georges, Susan M. (Box 9)
  - The Italian renaissance book., 1985; Grzeslo, Barbara (Box 10)
  - An essay on the graphic design of Alexey Brodovitch., 1985; Konetzka, Michael (Box 10)
  - Shape as visual language., 1985; Lausen, Marcia (Box 10)
  - Writing systems in African societies., 1985; Mafundikwa, Isaac (Box 10)
  - Lissitzky's contributions to graphic design., 1985; Odgis, Janet (Box 10)
  - Photography and language., 1985; Rodgers, Alan (Box 25)
  - A study of X., 1985; Rosenwald, Gina (Box 10)
  - In search of the Sonnet's design: proofs., 1985; Stern, Robert (Box 10)
    Includes 2 volumes; 1 volume of proofs.
  - Design in Paris: 1963-1973., 1985; Stern, Ani (Box 25)
  - Design by subtraction., 1985; Verba, Susan (Box 10)
  - Japanese typography: unique blend of cultures., 1985; Wells, Terry (Box 10)
  - The integration of word and picture in graphic design., 1985; Williams, David (Box 10)
  - Trademarks: factors leading to their anonymity., 1986; Bischoff, Robert (Box 10)
  - 20th century Dutch graphic design., 1986; Bodenweber, Joanna (Box 30)
  - Visual deceptions: ambiguity and paradox in graphic art., 1986; Hart, Peter (Box 10)
  - Color choice in graphic design, a red perspective., 1986; Hiltabiddle, Timothy (Box 10)
  - Designing information., 1986; Jacobson, Juliet (Box 11)
  - Japanese book design before 1868., 1986; Kitamura, Mayumi (Box 11)
  - Board games, graphic paradigms of the human experience., 1986; Larsen, Laurie (Box 11)
  - Lu Shu and graphic design--using Lu Shu, the six principles in creating Chinese characters in graphic design., 1986; Lee, Eddie H. S. (Box 11)
  - Rhythm in typography., 1986; Lee, Joanne (Box 11)
  - Redesigning the coat of arms of Puerto Rico., 1986; Maldonado, Mayra (Box 11)
  - Graphic design on stage., 1986; Marosek, Wallace (Box 11)
  - Political graphics of persuasion and terror., 1986; Muresanu, Marius (Box 11)
  - The rebus: and the rebus principle., 1986; Ouchi, Lisa N. (Box 11)
  - Rebirth of the scribe: the vulgarization of electrographic type design., 1986; Ross, Michael (Box 30)
  - Minaturization, an expanded view., 1986; Serafin, Priscilla (Box 11)
  - Time after time, a discussion of Western calendar diagrams contrasting the medieval and modern eras., 1986; Sherman, Meg (Box 11)
  - The star., 1986; Shoemaker, Patricia (Box 11)
  - Painters and letterforms., 1986; Tierney, Frank (Box 11)
  - Herbert Matter, the years in Paris and Zurich 1928-1936., 1986; Vanko, Lauren (Box 11)
  - A tablature system for the diatonic harmonica., 1987; Ambo, Bryce (Box 11)
  - Marinetti and the futurist revolution in typography., 1987; Barash, Andrea (Box 11)
  - Graphic design education Project with Armin Hofmann., 1987; Boman, Patricia M. (Box 11)
  - Contrast in visual design., 1987; Burns, Robert, 1759-1796 (Box 11)
  - Wine labels: tradition in contemporary design., 1987; Connacher, Nat (Box 11)
  - Rodchenko and the transformation of design., 1987; Délano, José (Box 11)
  - Word as image: the 20th century typographic poster., 1987; Guha, Sujata Keshavan (Box 12)
  - Ink on paper., 1987; Kugeler, Henry (Box 12)
  - Computer applications in graphic design education., 1987; Lindholm, Liisa (Box 12)
  - Bauhaus typography., 1987; Schunick, Susan (Box 12)
  - Untitled (something from nothing), 1987; Szujewska, Laurie; 2 (Box 12)
  - Visual texture: a study of the printed page., 1987; Tsang, Hayley (Box 12)
  - The problem of superficial design., 1987; Waldron, James (Box 12)
  - The good, the bad, and the ugly: reconsidering the vernacular and the workaday., 1987; Whistler, Mark (Box 25)
  - The influence of technology on graphic design., 1988; Altschul, Charles (Box 12)
  - Wish you were here the picture postcard., 1988; Anstett, Virginia (Box 12)
  - The evolution of a book die kunstismen., 1988; Devereux, Tara (Box 30)
  - The raven and the writing desk., 1988; Dire, John (Box 30)
  - Photography as a tool in graphic design education., 1988; Gaynor, Matthew (Box 25)
  - Four questions; a look at aesthetic issues in graphic design., 1988; Grover, Gaynelle (Box 12)
  - An investigation of the graphic translation., 1988; Hudson, Judith (Box 12)
  - Art S-132 introductory graphic design Yale summer program. June 21-August 11, 1988., Hyland, Sharka Brod (Box 12)
  - The unfinished Leonardo., 1988; Kaito, Carol Lee (Box 12)
  - The effect of context on the meaning of visual signs., 1988; Moore, Allen (Box 12)
  - An examination of the project at Yale University., 1988; Ocko, Beth S. (Box 12)
  - Sketches by graphic designers., 1988; Patterson, Wynne (Box 12)
  - Pierre Bonnard and his posters., 1988; Yo, Sok (Yo Po) (Box 12)
  - The transition of Chinese book design from the late ninteenth century to the 1930's., 1988; Wang, Min (Box 12)
  - Discussions of the gestalt of connected signs., 1988; Wilson, Sloane (Box 12)
  - Science + design: a new synthesis., 1988; Wu, Brian (Box 12)
  - AIDS education and graphic design., 1989; Blackburn, Timothy (Box 33)
  - The text as musical composition., 1989; Bush, Anne (Box 25)
    See also Box 30.
  - Rolling squarely in the great circle of languages., 1989; Calvert, Sheena (Box 12)
    See also Box 25.
  - Time as sequence., 1989; Faimon, Peggy (Box 12)
  - The comic spirit in graphic design., 1989; Gazley, Barbara (Box 12)
  - License to risk: the square revisited., 1989; Helfand, Jessica, 1960- (Box 12)
  - Accidents will happen: posters for a safe planet., 1989; Hight, Scott (Box 25)
  - On overcoming knowledge., 1989; Kasprowicz, Diane (Box 12)
  - Calligraphica: script letters and their use., 1989; Lehman, Peter (Box 12)
  - The word set free: expressive typography 1909-24., 1989; McDougal, Kristen (Box 30)
  - The sequential representation of motion., 1989; McKee, Stuart (Box 33)
  - The function of typographic ornament., 1989; Miller, Carla (Box 25)
  - Involving the viewer., 1989; Nesnadny, Joyce (Box 12)
  - Piet Zwart: the typographic work., 1989; Plank, Bruce (Box 12)
  - Phoenician alphabet: its origins and character., 1989; Saad, Walid (Box 30)
  - Herbert Matter's Giacometti., 1989; Taylor, Alex (Box 12)
  - Art or Design / Design or Art., 1989; Williams, J. P. (Box 13)
  - Photomontage and constructed realities., 1990; Balboni, Timothy (Box 25)
  - Beat: a typographic visualization of the narrative structure of part one of Jack Kerouac's On the road, 1990; Cooney, Christine Celano (Box 54)
  - Sensitizing/para-visual communication., 1990; Dobson, Terry M. (Box 22)
  - Sensitizing/para-visual communication., 1990; Dobson, Terry M. (Box 30)
  - Context., 1990; Geismar, Daphne (Box 54)
  - Sexuality in communication: representation of the male nude., 1990; Farés, Huda Abi (Box 30)
  - College: when twice two makes five., 1990; Hoot, Christopher (Box 13)
  - Modern Korean writing and typography., 1990; Kim, Hae Ok (Box 55)
  - Legends: reading the whole., 1990; Kirkpatrick, Garland; 2 (Box 13)
  - Typography., 1990; Moll, Donna (Box 13)
  - The interface between art and music / Ako Nakamura., 1990; Nakamura, Ako (Box 55)
  - Contrary and congruent: the typography of Jan Tschichoid., 1990; Pfeffer, Pamela Kim (Box 13)
  - Intuition in graphic design: a documented learning experience., 1990; Pincus, Julie (Box 13)
  - Design in miniature: 150 years of engraved postage stamps., 1990; Scaglia, Ken (Box 56)
    Includes 1 volume and 1 wooden crate.
  - Designing the defaults: graphic design defaults for users and programmers of desktop publishing systems: A presentation in HyperCard., 1990; Simard, Carol (Box 13)
  - This is not a cookbook: towards the depiction of process: a study of recipe design / Leslie S. Voit., 1990; Voit, Leslie S. (Box 55)
  - Invading space: three dimensional viewpoints., 1990; Wollensak, Andrea (Box 30)
  - High-resolution design: a crime map: a monitor display., 1990; Wong, Dona (Box 25)
  - Soviet film posters from the 20s and 80s., 1991; Bauer, Margaret (Box 25)
  - Insight: a design proposal for the New England Holocaust memorial competition., 1991; Boyiazis, Annie (Box 25)
  - In the interest of progress: a redesign of United States paper money., 1991; Burritt, Richard (Box 13)
  - Image as mnemonic device., 1991; Chang, Gloria (Box 13)
  - The gendered self in graphic design: interviews with 15 women designers., 1991; Fairbairn, Janet (Box 25)
  - Mapping the intellect., 1991; Laws, George (Box 30)
  - Chess as metaphor., 1991; Liebergesell, Alex (Box 30)
  - Bilingual books for children -- a children's book in English and Japanese., 1991; Matsui, Hisako (Box 13)
  - 991: a magazine of the moment., 1991; McKibben, James (Box 30)
  - AIDS activist design., 1991; Moss, Jimmy (Box 57)
    Includes 8 items.
  - Opening the test: a multi-voiced reconsideration of the Passover Haggadah., 1991; Smotrich, Hannah (Box 13)
  - Toward a social art: public art in New Haven., 1991; Towler, Cheryl (Box 13)
  - Sacred texts: image, sound and word in Christian, Hindu and Islamic traditions., 1991; Verma, Neeta (Box 30)
  - Critique of the design museum: the glass case syndrome., 1992; Abbot, Rodney (Box 13)
  - Youth culture and the ideology of style., 1992; Campbell, Ned (Box 25)
  - Support and resist: the photomontages of Gustav Klucis and John Heartfield., 1992; Canine, Steven (Box 30)
  - The point: an exploration of formal and symbolic issues., 1992; Friedman, Stuart (Box 13)
  - Narrative imagery in children's picture books., 1992; Gibb, Rebecca (Box 25)
  - Unifying the arts., 1992; Lam, Amy (Box 30)
  - Are you hungry?, 1992; Lynaugh, Matthew (Box 13)
  - Manifestations of Christian iconography: the body and consumption in contemporary culture., 1992; Mangano, Lisa (Box 30)
  - Non commercial graphic design in Switzerland and the reithelle of Bern., 1992; Marasek, Claudia (Box 13)
  - Redesign of the packages: reduction + reclamation., 1992; Min, Alexandra (Box 14)
  - Carried across: translating the photographic image through offset printing., 1992; Rosowsky, Lisa (Box 30)
  - The design of a tribal font: for Native American users., 1992; Scott, Resa (Box 14)
  - A cartographic analysis of the New Haven Railroad Line., 1992; Scranton, Bonnie (Box 14)
  - Clarity through obscurity., 1992; Shoglow, Lisa (Box 25)
  - Print media and the adolescent girl., 1992; Smith, Kathleen (Box 14)
  - Print media and the adolescent girl., 1992; Smith, Kathleen (Box 58)
    Includes 1 poster.
  - Prehistoric symbols of East Asia and North America., 1992; Tateno, Kyoko (Box 26)
  - Light years: the glass paintings of Josef Albers, 1912-1932., 1992; Tombs, Robert (Box 26)
  - Heroes between the wars., 1992; Weightman, Kenneth (Box 86)
  - Symmetry/asymmetry contrast between Chinese and Japanese aesthetics., 1993; Chan, Wilson (Box 26)
  - Recovering the textbook., 1993; Conant, Ellen (Box 26)
  - This is a purely visual experience., 1993; Drodvillo, Debra (Box 14)
  - Grammar and space., 1993; Hayes, Emily (Box 30)
  - Directions: the graphic language of maps and gameboards., 1993; Hill, Sally (Box 26)
  - Words in freedom: the sequel., 1993; Hovland, Pamela (Box 30)
  - Paisley, polka dot and plain., 1993; Huszar, Marta (Box 30)
  - Gone camping: an affectiion for bad graphic design., 1993; Maltais, Mark (Box 31)
  - Cultural evolution: a case study of the American Art Museum and its graphic design., 1993; Old, Constance (Box 26)
  - Chine word play as a source of graphic design concepts., 1993; Pat, Chun-Wo (Box 14)
  - The notated spectacle: representations of movement in space & time., 1993; Robbins, Juliette (Box 31)
  - Deconstructing chaos., 1993; Sandler, Catherine (Box 60)
  - Inspiration and re-creation a historical & visual treatise of Serif typefaces., 1993; Simon, Arlyn (Box 31)
  - Visual flow graphic design and cinematography: a comparison., 1993; Van Assen, Henk (Box 31)
  - From victims to victors: women making themselves and their work visible., 1994; Ashworth, Lisa (Box 14)
  - Stopping time., 1994; Bernstein, Jennifer (Box 14)
  - Graphic design and outreach., 1994; Cadwallader, Diana (Box 14)
    Includes 3 volumes.
  - Made in Taiwan: more than just a label., 1994; Chou, Hsien-yin (Ingrid) (Box 61)
  - Ads interruptus., 1994; Comberg, David (Box 14)
  - Finding my way., 1994; Gifford, Daniel (Box 14)
  - I know this woman...she has seven chairs., 1994; Goodwin, Amy (Box 14)
  - Visual poetics: an exploration of words in space., 1994; Hitchcock, Lucy (Box 14)
  - Exalted and degraded: the orient as spectacle., 1994; Kim, Jeanne (Box 26)
  - Ilia-Zdanevich ILIAZD., 1994; Krasny, Dmitry (Box 14)
  - Sticks & stones., 1994; Nishinaka, Yuki (Box 26)
  - Gazing black: Representations of African American women in magazine advertising., 1994; Richmond, Cathy (Box 14)
  - Typeface, typography, and the design of reading material for the visually impaired., 1994; Schreiber, Patrick (Box 15)
  - Beyond pro bono., 1994; Spencer, Jeanne (Box 15)
  - Gendered masculine: representation in the New York Times., 1994; Starr, Thomas (Box 76)
  - Julia de Burgos: public memory and bi-cultural recognition., 1994; Weil, Rafael (Box 15)
  - Wayfinding in the digital terrain., 1994; Whitney, Julia (Box 15)
  - The dual realities of the grid., 1995; Chan, Jenny (Box 15)
  - Considering wallpaper as graphic design., 1995; Clarke, Vickie (Box 15)
  - Subjectivity and expression: an approach to information design., 1995; Duffy, Katya (Box 15)
  - Graphic design and film: the space between as a narrative tool., 1995; Flaxman, Cynthia (Box 31)
  - Girl talkin'., 1995; Hall, Colleen (Box 15)
  - Looking deep: fragmentation/style/meaning., 1995; Israel, David (Box 15)
  - The total grid., 1995; Kusters, Christian (Box 15)
  - Discovering the Kuan-Yin ritual through graphic design., 1995; Lim, Yan-Peng (Box 15)
  - Kitschy coups., 1995; Olsztyn, Mark (Box 15)
  - Invisible structures: the element of context in visual interface design., 1995; Paul, Christopher (Box 16)
  - Text and dialogue: orality in the electronic environment., 1995; Radeka, Dina (Box 26)
  - I see what you mean: a new way of learning through the digital medium., 1995; Sebata, Yuri (Box 16)
  - This too shall pass: re-examining ethemera., 1995; Stearns, Sarah (Box 16)
  - From universal to individual: issues of audience in graphic design., 1995; Thaw, Jacqueline (Box 16)
  - Aesthetization of the corporation., 1995; Yegir, Edvin (Box 16)
  - Being there designing information., 1995; Wu, Weilin (Box 16)
  - Cross cultural duality., 1996; Abraham, Guenet (Box 26)
  - Changing perspectives., 1996; Cassuto, Michelle (Box 16)
  - The typographic-spectacular landscape., 1996; Connolly, John (Box 16)
  - Myth, realism, and videotape., 1996; Devis, Macala (Box 16)
  - Super language: decoding consumer graphics., 1996; Fener, Heidi (Box 16)
  - Keep in touch., 1996; Hamilton, Peter (Box 31)
  - Counter-intelligence., 1996; Henley, Stuart (Box 16)
  - On technology and design., 1996; Ho, Dave (Box 16)
  - Seal as personal mark., 1996; Kim, Kyung (Box 16)
  - Mas typography: towards an aesthetic of carnival., 1996; Lawrence, Michael (Box 31)
  - Fixing memory., 1996; McDonald, Ann (Box 26)
  - Body of information., 1996; Oliveri, Jamie (Box 27)
  - Invisible city., 1996; Roos, Jennifer (Box 16)
  - The graphic design professional., 1996; Routhier, Charles (Box 16)
  - Here, there, and graphic design., 1996; Singh, Tania (Box 27)
  - Deux ex machina., 1996; Sullivan, Thomas (Box 27)
  - Pop soup., 1996; Thompson, Beverly (Box 16)
  - For my baby my legacy., 1997; Bennett, Audrey (Box 62)
    Includes 26 blocks, 6 cards, and 1 mesh bag
  - Public design., 1997; Brady, Megan (Box 27)
  - Cinematic highway., 1997; Ceria, Arthur (Box 16)
    Includes 1 VHS.
  - Cinematic highway., 1997; Ceria, Arthur (Box 32)
  - Design space: conversations around a graphic fire., 1997; Chamy, Dimitry (Box 16)
  - The book: icon, artifact & art form., 1997; Filene, Rebecca (Box 16)
  - Body as measure., 1997; Hardy, Penelope (Box 17)
  - Observations in public space: a closer look at common ground., 1997; Hurlbut, Ann W. (Box 27)
  - Octothorp: eight audiences around a central field., 1997; Krupnik, Anya (Box 27)
  - Story., 1997; Kruperminc, Melissa (Box 27)
  - Identity crisis., 1997; Maley, Kimberley (Box 17)
  - Urban landscapes., 1997; Moochhala, Niloufer (Box 17)
  - Artificial portraits., 1997; Opara, Eddie (Box 17)
  - Authored topographies., 1997; Plesko, George (Box 17)
  - Input / output: being + technology., 1997; Tarnowski, Kirsten (Box 17)
  - Masking identity., 1997; Zwirn, Randy (Box 17)
  - Border culture: graphic design and the topographies of difference., 1998; Akselsen, Bjorn (Box 17)
  - Traveling with infinite velocity., 1998; Black, Margaret (Box 17)
  - Beginnings [ ] endings., 1998; Corcoran, Heather (Box 27)
  - Regarding celebrity., 1998; Howell, Courtney (Box 27)
  - Generative systems., 1998; Hsieh, Pei (Box 63)
  - K corporation., 1998; Hsu, Karen Ting (Box 17)
  - Mixing olive oil and soy sauce: orientation of my cultural identity., 1998; K'ang, Claire Wei (Box 17)
  - Unfamiliar dimensions., 1998; Kim, Stephanie Hyun Jung (Box 17)
  - Zero world: report 1998., Massey, Richard (Box 17)
  - Longings., 1998; McGinty, Miko (Box 17)
  - Leaving land., 1998; Melcher, Charles B. (Box 17)
  - Catalog 1995-98., 1998; Sanematsu, Helen (Box 17)
  - Meditative process, meditative object., 1998; Sernsukskul, Serena (Box 27)
  - Contemporary graphic design: evolution through redefinition., 1998; Theobald, Claire (Box 18)
  - Private iconography: symbols as domestic language., 1998; Vatanapahu, Pacharin (Box 18)
  - Food: designing choice., 1998; Weese, Catherine (Box 18)
  - Everyday Views: Designed as Frame., 1999; Apte, Ariel (Box 18)
  - Eating the Recipe: choreography of the everyday., 1999; Cheng, Alicia (Box 76)
  - Clue in the Jewel Box., 1999; Church, Stephanie (Box 18)
  - Dear Crayola Explorations in colorful language., 1999; Garvin, Courtney (Box 18)
  - Instructions: Some Assembly Required., 1999; Gephart, Sarah (Box 18)
  - Daddy: Here now nowhere., 1999; Jasper, Daniel (Box 31)
  - Do it yourself activism and the art of being subar., 1999; Naples, Alysha (Box 64)
  - What Is Real?, 1999; Kim, Boyeun (Box 18)
  - Cyclical experiences., 1999; Kim, Sung Hyun (Box 18)
  - Scratching the surface: Intuitive expression in the graphic design process., 1999; Lamour, Kristina (Box 19)
  - Days of Confusion Living with the two languages, 1999; Muroga, Takayo (Box 19)
  - Temporary Thesis., 1999; Reinfurt, David (Box 19)
  - Designing books. Practice and theory., 1999; Villaflor, Robert (Box 19)
  - Virtual Topographies., 2000; Campbell, Collin (Box 19)
  - Invoking ingenuity., 2000; Churchman, Laurie (Box 19)
  - Fictive veracities., 2000; Ellis, Elizabeth (Box 19)
  - The 212: Projects one to twenty six., 2000; Enriquez, Vanessa (Box 19)
  - Cool dry place., 2000; Fry, Julie (Box 19)
  - Placed., 2000; Hartley, Josh (Box 31)
  - Space media labs 98 - 00., 2000; Jones, Kevin H. (Box 19)
  - Orange island., 2000; Ko, Hong (Box 31)
  - Yale's best thesis: an exploration of incongruity, false authority, and dark humor., 2000; Kuhnau, Darren (Box 19)
  - Zero, my hero., 2000; Ma, Jung-Min (Box 65)
  - Materials and memories., 2000; Mark, Jonathan Skyler (Box 19)
  - Writing city space., 2000; Owens, Mark (Box 20)
  - Surface: the aesthetics of obsolescence..., 2000; Robinson, Cheyney (Box 20)
  - Citizens of nowhere., 2000; Suh, Alex Y. (Box 20)
  - Life in the margins based on a true story., 2000; Taylor, Leila (Box 20)
  - Repetition and difference., 2000; Wei, Li (Box 20)
  - Open me., 2000; Yampolsky, Hannah (Box 20)
  - Multiplicity deciphered, sort of., 2001; De Luna, Elizabeth (Box 66)
    Includes 1 folder and 1 newspaper.
  - See what I'm saying., 2001; Elsas, Elizabeth (Box 20)
  - Universal unique., 2001; Frisco, David (Box 20)
  - Alternative use: relative and reuse., 2001; Fukushime, Shelly (Box 20)
  - Ashphalt Libretto., 2001; Geiling, Darina (Box 20)
  - Meta-thesis., 2001; Hoyt, Randall (Box 76)
  - Sounds per inch., 2001; Lau, Jen (Box 21)
  - This space for rent., 2001; Lee, Chae (Box 21)
  - Desktop: metaphor, myth, Mold., 2001; Lin, Alex (Box 21)
  - Detourism., 2001; Maletic, Tamara (Box 31)
  - An exhibition., 2001; Ouellet, Nadine (Box 21)
  - Please pause., 2001; Shen, Elain (Box 31)
  - One-on-one., 2001; Tomsits, Kristin (Box 21)
  - Buried echoes: excavating visible history., 2001; Tucker, Lesley (Box 21)
  - Minding the gap., 2001; Zurolo, Mark (Box 31)
  - Allegorithm., 2002; Cezzar, Juliette (Box 75)
  - TRash TReasure., 2002; Cho, Hyun (Box 69)
  - Thesis 731: visibility, surveillance and graphic design., 2002; Choi, Sung Min (Box 69)
  - Scan., 2002; Cummings, Glen (Box 75)
  - Under the influence: Investigations in cultural addiction., 2002; Espiritu, Allan (Box 75)
  - This is now_Thesis now., 2002; Kim, Kenneth (Box 69)
  - Teaching martial arts., 2002; Kim, Sang Do (Box 69)
  - Ficciones., 2002; Kim, Sung Joong; 7; parts (Box 67)
  - trans-(prefix) across, beyond, through, so as to change., 2002; Lee, Ahree (Box 69)
  - Thick and thin., 2002; Michaelson, Dan (Box 65)
  - In part., 2002; Ponce, Margarita Barrios (Box 69)
  - Handling distance., 2002; Ross, Rebecca (Box 69)
  - From up below to down above., 2002; Suh, Deena (Box 69)
  - Search by?, 2002; Valentine, Jonty (Box 75)
  - Search by?, 2002; Valentine, Jonty (Box 75)
  - Theory/ Reality., 2003; Budnitz, Alexander (Box 69)
  - Diagrams., 2003; Choi, Sulki (Box 68)